<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>


        <string-array name="ConsequencesOrMission">
            <item>Consequences</item>
            <item>Mission</item>
        </string-array>
        
        <string-array name="Consequences">
            <item>Eat a tablespoon of mayonnaise. </item>
            <item>Whisper the rest of the game. </item>
            <item>Take and post a selfie with food between your teeth. </item>
            <item>Repeat the previous consequence performed. </item>
            <item>Swallow a teaspoon of cinnamon. </item>
            <item>Have any player draw something you do not know what\'s on your face. </item>
            <item>Shave a leg or an armpit. </item>
            <item>Message "MILF" to a mother </item>
            <item>The group chooses which player\'s armpit to put your nose in. </item>
            <item>Turn on an 80\'s song and dance high school drummer with the player to the left until time runs out. </item>
            <item>Eat a tablespoon of butter. </item>
            <item>Open up your fly and sit for the rest of the game. Disgusting! </item>
            <item>Keep your underwear in the freezer for 20 minutes, then put it back on. </item>
            <item>Hold hands with the players next to you until it\'s your turn again. </item>
            <item>Mess with someone who is not in the room with a detailed description of what you are wearing. </item>
            <item>Make 30 jumping jacks. </item>
            <item>Eat quite a lot of uncooked pasta. </item>
            <item>Kiss a player on the mouth </item>
            <item>Eat a deciliter of ketchup. </item>
            <item>Sit on a player\'s lap until it\'s your turn again. </item>
            <item>The player on the left determines a consequence for you. </item>
            <item>Suck on a tea bag until it\'s your turn again. </item>
            <item>Lean back. Choose a player who can put one of his socks on your face until it\'s your turn again </item>
            <item>Swap base with one player for the rest of the game. </item>
            <item>Select a player and one of their feet. Now remove the dirt between the toes. </item>
            <item>Lick a player on the cheek. </item>
            <item>Spank yourself or a volunteer. </item>
            <item>Various skins! Take off three garments and put them back on. </item>
            <item>Change relationship status to “Engaged”. </item>
            <item>Drink one deciliter of oil. </item>
            <item>Message “DILF” to a Dad. </item>
            <item>The group may choose an inappropriate sentence to say aloud each time it is your turn. </item>
            <item>Choose a player, take off a sock and kiss any part of their foot. </item>
            <item>Turn your clothes inside out </item>
            <item>Eat a banana sensually. </item>
            <item>Let the player on the left roll on the floor through the room. </item>
            <item>Have the player on the left write and post a Facebook status for you. </item>
            <item>Give all players a high five. </item>
            <item>Eat a clove of garlic. </item>
            <item>Let the cabbage drinker on the left draw a unibrow on you. </item>
            <item>Change birthday on Facebook. </item>
            <item>Lick your initials on the table. Hopefully it\'s pretty clean. </item>
            <item>Let the puck on the right freely style your hair. </item>
            <item>Stand up until it\'s your turn again. </item>
            <item>Paint your nails on yourself or a volunteer. </item>
            <item>Award a Most Likely prize to each player. (Example: Most likely to go to jail) </item>
            <item>Swap a shirt with one player for the rest of the game. </item>
            <item>Next time you go to the bathroom, do not close the door. </item>
            <item>Let the crunch ball on the left change the PIN code of your phone. </item>
            <item>Repeat the previous consequence that was run. </item>
            <item>Close your eyes and scroll through your images. Select an image and view the group before opening your eyes. </item>
            <item>Licking a player\'s earlobe. </item>
            <item>Friend-request a friend\'s parent. </item>
            <item>Drink a drink that the other players mix for you. </item>
            <item>Like: an old picture of your ex. </item>
            <item>Drink four glasses of water. </item>
            <item>Let the youngest player go through the pictures on your mobile and show any picture to the players. </item>
            <item>Drink two glasses of water. </item>
            <item>Let the player on the right write and post a Facebook status for you. </item>
            <item>You\'re now a cock head! Have someone draw a cock on your head. </item>
            <item>Change the profile picture to your most recent picture on your phone. </item>
            <item>Wash. Seriously; go to the kitchen and do the dishes. </item>
            <item>Confuse your parents with a series of emojis without context. </item>
            <item>Drink a raw egg </item>
            <item>Let the player on the right delete a contact on your phone. </item>
            <item>Try licking your elbow while singing the alphabet. </item>
            <item>Swish SEK 50 to another player. </item>
            <item>Get something to drink for the player on the left! </item>
            <item>Let the player on the left write and send sms to any contact. </item>
            <item>Give all players a kiss on the cheek. </item>
            <item>Mess any player until it\'s your turn again. </item>
            <item>Draw your mother until it\'s your turn again and then send the picture to her. Be proud! </item>
            <item>Eat a teaspoon of salt. </item>
            <item>Get a toilet roll and make yourself a mummy. </item>
            <item>Go outdoors and offer the first person you see a hug. </item>
            <item>Hug all the other players </item>
            <item>Let the idiot on the right draw something on your arm. Take photos and post with the caption "New tattoo!" </item>
            <item>Tell us about a crush you had on an adult as a child. </item>
            <item>Let the player on the left delete any contact from your phone. </item>
            <item>Go to the toilet with any cabbage drinker and do not come out until it\'s your turn again. </item>
            <item>Let the player on the right write and send an SMS to any contact. </item>
            <item>Stand up and spin 15 laps. </item>
            <item>Swish a player 20 bucks. </item>
            <item>Imitate what everyone says during two rounds. </item>
            <item>Fair a Porn hub link to a family member. </item>
            <item>Do 20 push-ups. </item>
            <item>Swish SEK 75 to another player. </item>
            <item>Get a drink for the player on the right! </item>
            <item>Put on your shoes and tie them together. Then have the rest of the game. </item>
            <item>Are you good or not? Talk like a Gothenburger the rest of the game. Everyone who bothers is from Västerås. </item>
            <item>The player on the right determines a consequence for you. </item>
            <item>Suck continuously on your thumb until it\'s your turn again. </item>
            <item>Borrow an egg from the neighbor. </item>
            <item>Imse vimse, yes how is the rest going? Stand up and sing the whole song, complete with male gestures. </item>
            <item>Hope you used deodorant today! Put your hands on your head and keep them there until it\'s your turn again. </item>
            <item>Recognize which players you are attracted to. </item>
            <item>Wear socks for the rest of the game. </item>
            <item>Shave your arms. </item>
            <item>Take a sip from all players\' glasses. </item>
            <item>Stand up and spin 10 laps. </item>
            <item>Go to the bathroom and rinse your face with cold water. Come back and keep playing without drying yourself out. </item>
            <item>Clear any player\'s umbilical cord. </item>
            <item>Delete your Instagram account. </item>
            <item>Give the column on the left 4 true compliments. </item>
            <item>Put a finger in the sock. </item>
            <item>Melt an ice cube in your mouth. </item>
            <item>Hope the player on the left has clean feet! Take off one sock and give foot massage until the time is up. </item>
            <item>Delete your twitter account. </item>
            <item>Do everything you are asked to do until it\'s your turn again. </item>
            <item>Hold hands with a player next to you until it\'s your turn again. </item>
            <item>Let the group take an embarrassing picture of you. They decide how you pose. </item>
            <item>Describe your underwear in detail. </item>
            <item>Eat a tablespoon, either mustard, soy or chili sauce. </item>
            <item>Take a picture holding up any item selected by the leading player. Post photos on social media with the caption “;)” </item>
            <item>Replace the top with an optional boom. </item>
            <item>Standing like an X is your turn again. </item>
            <item>Post a lottery winning status. </item>
            <item>Kiss a player on the butt. </item>
            <item>Hang something around your neck that is not normally a piece of jewelry. </item>
            <item>Report sick tomorrow. </item>
            <item>Swish SEK 100 to the player on the left. </item>
            <item>Get something to drink for all but one. </item>
            <item>Swish SEK 100 to the player on the right. </item>
            <item>Swap socks with another player. </item>
            <item>Post an ultrasound image on social media. The image may be removed after 24 hours. </item>
            <item>String your underwear and have the rest of the game. </item>
            <item>Tear off your underwear. </item>
            <item>Cartwheel. </item>
            <item>Go to the bathroom and change: Wear the underwear on top of the clothes for the rest of the game. </item>
            <item>Message "Thinking of you." To your mother. </item>
            <item>Take a bite of an onion as if it were an apple. </item>
            <item>Draw a genital on your hand. </item>
        </string-array>
    
        <string-array name="Mission">
            <item>Stand on one leg, sit on a chair and stand on one leg again. You must not use your hands. </item>
            <item>Move your fingers behind your back, with one arm over your head and the other from below. </item>
            <item>Stand up, lift a chair and hold it in front of you with straight arms until it\'s your turn again. </item>
            <item>Put this card upside down and walk backwards around the table. The card must not fall before you sit down. </item>
            <item>Read the alphabet backwards. For each error, you must start from the beginning. You have 3 attempts. </item>
            <item>Pick up your phone from the floor with your foot and place it on the table. You have a try. </item>
            <item>Leave the room. The other players hide the game phone. You have until a player loses patience with you to find it! </item>
            <item>Lick a piece of paper, attach it to your forehead, leave it until it\'s your turn again. </item>
            <item>On with blindfolds and guess what three items the group gives you! If you get all right, you get </item>
            <item>Select a player and write their name backwards on your forehead. </item>
            <item>Say seven Swedish cities starting with K. </item>
            <item>Call a friend and turn on the speaker. Can you get him to say "Pingisboll" without saying any part of the word himself. </item>
            <item>Burp "Kalabala" You have two attempts. </item>
            <item>Ear file yourself. If you do, all other players must file themselves. </item>
            <item>Choose a player you think has more leg hair than you. </item>
            <item>Choose a player and guess the color of their underwear. </item>
            <item>Select a player to tickle. Do you manage to make him laugh </item>
            <item>Lay the gaming phone on the floor. Simply jump back and forth over it 10 times without the other foot touching the floor. </item>
            <item>Hold your nose and hold your breath for one minute. </item>
            <item>Call a friend and have them say "Ivory Coast" without saying a word. </item>
            <item>Choose a player to sing the entire first verse of "You old you free". You get points. </item>
            <item>Google and show Goatse to everyone. </item>
            <item>You have until it\'s your turn to find at least two of the following: Hammer, beech, potted plant and spoon. </item>
            <item>Select a player to sing the entire lyrics to any children\'s song. </item>
            <item>Toss a coin and guess right on the crown or piano. At the right guess plus points. </item>
            <item>All players sitting down when this card is finished reading must kiss you on the cheek. </item>
            <item>Say 5 Swedish cities starting with H. </item>
            <item>Say four countries ending in "country". </item>
            <item>Light a lighter 5 times in a row. </item>
            <item>Stand up and touch your toes with straight legs. </item>
            <item>Challenge a player on a Scissors bag, if you win you get points. </item>
            <item>Say six Swedish cities starting with S. </item>
            <item>Say seven Swedish cities that contain “Köping”. </item>
            <item>Place a coin on your elbow and catch it with your hand. You need to pass 3 out of 5 attempts. </item>
            <item>Sit in the tailor position and stand up without using your hands. </item>
            <item>Say eight capitals before time runs out. </item>
            <item>Balance a book in your hand for five seconds. One of the corners of the book should be in the palm of your hand. </item>
            <item>Tell us something about yourself. The group guesses if what you are telling is true or false. Guess gives you points. </item>
            <item>Blink one eye at a time. </item>
            <item>You have until it\'s your turn again to find an insect, living or dead. </item>
            <item>You should play a movie scene, if your teammates guess correctly you will get points. </item>
            <item>You have until it\'s your turn again to make any tölp laugh by showing any body part. </item>
            <item>Stand on your head for 10 seconds. You have 2 attempts. </item>
            <item>Get a coin to spin, you get two tries. </item>
            <item>Guess the total number of tattoos the other players have. If you guess correctly, you get points. </item>
            <item>Each time you make eye contact with another player, you must shout "Cuba". </item>
            <item>Throw something in the air and catch it with your mouth. You must pass at least 2 out of 5 attempts. </item>
            <item>Find a cell phone charger, a hat and a board game, you\'ve got it your turn again. </item>
            <item>Open your arms completely and close your eyes. Can your middle fingers meet in front of your face? You must pass at least 2 of 3 attempts. </item>
            <item>Make a U with your tongue. </item>
            <item>Sing a verse from a song with a personal name in it. Swap the name for another player\'s. </item>
            <item>Make a coin spin and then stop it without the coin settling. You have two attempts. </item>
            <item>You\'re a squirrel getting ready for winter! Fill your pockets, sweater, pants, etc. with stuff. You have until it\'s your turn again. </item>
            <item>Lie on the floor and keep your legs up at a 45 degree angle until it\'s your turn again. </item>
            <item>Find a potato peeler, a light bulb and a ball before time runs out. </item>
            <item>Can you whistle Johanna? You whistle one song, the others guess. </item>
        </string-array>

    <string-array name="RandomTaskArrayOfColors">
        <item>Blue</item>
        <item>Purple</item>
        <item>Red</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="RandomTaskArrayOfFeel">
        <item>Soft</item>
        <item>Hard</item>
        <item>Jiggly</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="RandomTaskArrayOfShape">
        <item>Round</item>
        <item>Rectangular</item>
        <item>Square</item>
        <item>Triangular</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="RandomTaskArrayOfCons">
        <item>One flick on the right ear</item>
        <item>One flick the left ear</item>
        <item>A pat on the head</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>